Philipp Eibl

Profile

Currently pursuing a Computer Science Specialist with a focus on Artificial Intelligence at the University of Toronto. I work best in teams and love to take on new challenges. I am most interested in question answering and transformer-based language models.

Education

Bachelor of Science, University of Toronto (St. George)

September 2019 — Present, Toronto, ON, Canada

Computer Science Specialist (Focus in Artificial Intelligence)

Bachelor of Science, University of British Columbia

September 2019 — May 2019, Kelowna, BC, Canada

Summer School, Harvard University

June 2015 — August 2015, Cambridge, MA, USA

Experience

Software Development Intern at Arctic Wolf

September 2021—present, Toronto, ON, Canada

Worked in the data processing unit of the threat detection pipeline.

Research Assistant at Simon Fraser University

September 2021—present, Vancouver, BC, Canada

NLP engineer in SFU's discourse lab under Maite Taboada.

Full Stack Development at Antimatter

April 2019 — October 2019, Toronto, ON, Canada

Full Stack Development at the University of British Columbia

December 2018 — March 2019, Kelowna, BC, Canada

Full Stack Web App Development at MuseHQ (Metaplug.io)

May 2019 — August 2019, San Jose, CA, USA

Native Mobile App Development at Deine Seite

September 2019 — December 2019, Vienna, Austria

Extra-curricular

ML Engineer at CAN-SBX

September 2019 — September 2019, Timmins, ON, Canada

Walnut AI: Text Summary Generator (using k-Means Clustering)

November 2019 — Present

Airnotes: MacOS Notes App

September 2019 — Present

Details

Toronto, Canada, (250) 258-6655 philipp.eibl@mail.utoronto.ca

Courses (University of Toronto)

NLP CSC401

Computational Linguistics CSC485

Neural Networks CSC413

Intro to AI CSC386

Machine Learning CSC311

Data Structures & Algorithms CSC263

Enriched Statistics & Probability STA257

Numerical Methods CSC336

Papers

Word embeddings in question answering

Skills

NLP (language models, neural approaches, word embeddings, transformer-based architectures)

ML (NNs, Bayesian Models, GAN, ...)

OOP (Python, Java)

Data Science (Numpy, Scipy, PyTorch)

React (Redux, HTML, SASS, JS)

Mobile Development, Shell Scripting

Databases (MongoDB, SQL, Firebase)

Links

linkedin.com/in/philippeibl github.com/philippnoah philippnoah.github.io antimatter.studio (deprecated)

Languages

English, German (mother tongue), French, Italian